# Robin Maneiro Gesto

Bradford, United Kingdom robin.maneiro@gmail.com 07395246451

C.			
0	um	ım	arv

System administrator and hardware installer since I was 18. Currently, I am self-training in Software Development using Java language. I always strive to achieve the best results I can, and dedicate myself to my passion, which IT industry has become. Throughout my experience to date, I have enhanced my analytical and problem-solving skills, which I believe are the key strengths in computing.

# Experience

### Waiter & Supervisor

The Koop ~ February 2019 - July 2019

- Serve food and beverages, at the same time that check the deliveries.
- Supervise and optimize the duties of a small team of people, make orders and count the money.

### IT Technical Support

R Cable and Telecomunications (Spanish Operator)~ January 2017 - December 2018

- Provide a high level of customer service and communication to end users
- Provide support to technical engineers in Microsoft Server 2016 (Active Directory, GPO, DNS & DHCP)
- Provide support managing mailboxes over Microsoft Exchange
- Provide support to end users in Office 365 (Word, Excel and Outlook)
- \* Routing and Switching ( Ubiquiti, Lancom & Cisco )
- Support VoIP Telephone Systems (Asterisk & Grandstream)

#### IT Administrator & Technician

Exon Dynamics ~ October 2014 - January 2017

- Installation and maintenance of Windows based servers (Windows Server 2008 & 2012)
- ♦ Installation of computer equipment (Windows (7/8/10), Linux and Mac)
- Maintenance of computers in an Active Directory environment (GPO, MS Exchange, Shared Resources, etc)
- Installation of virtualized environments with VMware ESXi and VMware WorkSpace
- Cloning Windows systems using deployment software like Acronis Snap and Deploy
- Maintenance and diagnosis of any failure caused by a software, hardware or network issue.
- Network printers installation and configuration.

#### System Administrator & PBX Installer

Pronet Systems Telecom SLU ~ June 2008 - August 2013

- ♦ Installation of Windows based servers (Windows Server 2003 & 2008)
- Installation of computers (Windows, Linux and Mac)
- Network deployment and network equipment installation.
- **OCTV** and IP surveillance systems
- Installation of PBX systems: Panasonic (TA/TD/TES/TDA/NCP), OKI(IP-Stage), Neris (
  2/4/8/64) and Samsung, Siemens and Alcatel knowledge.
- Installation of Asterisk VoIP systems.

# Qualifications

### TOEIC 4 Skills (Total Score: B1 - 985)

- o Listening & Reading (Score: 715/990)
- o Speaking & Writing (Speaking Score: 110/200 | Writing Score: 160/200)

ETS ~ December 2018

## Oracle Certified Associate - Java Programmer I

Oracle Academy ~ September 2018

## Java Foundations Certified Junior Associate

Oracle Academy ~ June 2018

### General Certificate of Education (GCE)

Ies Isidro Parga Pondal ~ 2006-2008

Languages

- ♦ English Fluent
- Spanish Native Speaker
- Galician Native Speaker
- Portuguese Good command